

# **Contact**

andriivlasiuk2@gmail.com

+32 456 12 8979

Brussels, 1000

https://www.linkedin.com/in/a ndrii-vlasiuk-b0030789/

https://github.com/andriivam

## **Hard Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS
- GIT
- Postgres
- JavaScript
- · React.js
- Next JS
- Node.js
- Strapi
- Agile

# **Soft Skills**

- Adaptability
- Teamwork
- Communication

# Languages

- Russian & Ukrainian: native
- English: fluent
- French: basic

## **Hobbies**

- Travelling
- Coding

# **Education Background**

#### **Hack Your Future**

Frontend Web Developer

March 2022 - December 2022 | Belgium

#### **Kyiv National University of Trade and Economics**

Master in Health resort business September 2010 - January 2016 | Ukraine

# Andrii Vlasiuk

# Junior Web Developer

#### **About Me**

With over 8 years of extensive international experience and leadership in the fields of hospitality, and more recently 2 years in web development, I demonstrated and improved my ability to work as an effective team player, to adapt and adjust myself to diverse and changing environments.

Currently I am looking for a new challenging position as a web developer focusing on software as a service products that are driven by innovation, research, and experimentation.

# **Professional Experience**

#### 2023/07 - Present

· Actively searching for a job as Junior Web Developer to put into practice my capacity to both work independently and as part of the

#### Al Developer | Fari (Al for the common good) 2023/04 - 2023/06

- Creating multilingual demo project for FARI Center based on a "Replicate AP"I and "Next JS". It provides the user different types of inputs and get different types of outputs based on his choices.
- Connect to the "CMS Strapi"

## Junior Web Developer (Trainee) | BeCode

2022/09 - 2023/04 | Belgium

BeCode is an intensive 7 months coding bootcamp with active pedagogy. Here are couple of my projects:

- Weather App in frontend and backend with JavaScript, using the DOM, API's.
- ToDo List app, using React.
- Team Project: based on Agile methodology website which allows users, who sign-up, become a chef and sell home made food for other users

#### Waiter | CowFish 2019/09 - 2022/09 | Belgium

- Supervised food distribution, managed order placement, and facilitated seamless communication with the kitchen for order processing
- Developed opening and closing formalities

#### Food and beverage supervisor | VinPearl

#### 2018/07 - 2019/03 | Vietnam

- · Resolved guest complains & managed relations
- Developed weekly roaster, daily reports, informed staff about daily targets, analysed performance

# Assistant Manager | Red Cafe

2017/04 - 2018/05 | Cyprus

- Managed colleagues, distributed tasks by working areas and enabled daily and weekly reports
- Closing and opening the of restaurant

#### Waiter | Hilton Kyiv

2014/08 - 2016/07 | Ukraine

- Implemented conference set up according with BEO (Banquet Event Order)
- Supported other F&B outlets